This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Mocky D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
This sight!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will come a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
After being separated from Mr. Three and Buggy in this starvation hell,
Luffy and Bon Clay continued to fight their way to the lower levels,
excluding Saldes, I want all forces in the prison down on level four now!
Yes, sir! Of course, sir! Right away!
If Minotaurus fails us and they do find the way down,
once they set foot on this floor,
I will bury them with my own hands.
That is a lot of smoke!
Don't tell me we have to go down there!
Oh, it's bad enough up here on the ledge!
Alas, this is the burning hate hell you so desire to visit.
And double alas, it lives up to its name quite accurately.
Well, damn.
So what's down there?
And what are you two doing here?
I thought you said you were going to break out!
Not you again, dammit!
I knew you'd change your mind and come with me!
Screw you! I hope that thing eats you alive!
Either way, take this, you bastard!
My special weapon, the Muggy Ball!
All right! Now, come, come!
Alas, fight!
Yeah, we did it! We really did it!
We beat the monster, Calphi, from hell!
All forces have gathered!
The battle on level four, the burning heat hell!
How much time is left before they execute Ace?
29 hours.
It'll all be over by 3 p.m. tomorrow.
That's the plan, anyway.
Not that plans always go the way they're supposed to.
Portgas D. Ace is safe for the time being.
We'll transfer him in the morning.
Luffy, I pray that you're safe more than anything.
That's all I want.
All right, I'm going to ask you this one more time.
Huh?
After this, do you still honestly want to go down to level four?
Yeah! I knew you guys would come with me.
There's no way you're getting me down there.
I already feel like my skin's melting off my bones.
What is it going to take to make you realize it is too damn hot?
Does the boiling cauldron of flood and fire sound like a good time to you?
What about burning heat hell don't you get?
We are not going down there.
Aw, why?
It's pretty obvious.
We want to go up, not down.
Up! Up!
Yeah!
We're trying to escape and that's up.
Don't you get it?
Man, that is one really big bloody booger I just picked.
You're not even listening!
Just let them run away, straw boy.
They clearly don't have the balls to go one step further.
Hey! Even my nose is a damn ball!
You're what? Really?
That is weird.
Okay, we are getting off topic here.
How about you stop pulling my tail and I'll get back to spinning?
We've got some brilliant minds here.
Hey, is it just me or does it look like the ceiling is going up?
Ah, yeah, you're right it is.
Yeah?
There's kind of a loud rumbling too.
And you know this rushing sensation, it sort of feels like...
The ceiling's not rising! We're falling!
Oh, no!
My muggy ball must have been so powerful it caused the floor to collapse.
You wish!
It was the force of my heavy kick that did it!
You're both wrong.
It's because my punch was so strong it sent out Shockwave!
No, no, no.
My wax wax power.
Wait, I guess it didn't really do that much, actually.
Or is it shut up?
We're pulling into Hellfire!
Help us!
Please don't do this, sir!
Please don't kill us!
You deserve whatever happens to you.
That's the way justice works.
How many people have begged you not to kill them?
It's over.
But we deeply regret what we've done!
Yeah!
We're sorry!
Honestly!
No!
Please don't!
It burns!
Keep moving!
Lock that firewood!
It's too hot!
My body!
Even my guts are burning!
I'd rather die than put up with this!
I'm running for it!
Get out of my damn way!
I'm through with it!
We've got a prisoner escaping!
Hey!
Move it!
Go on!
Or you'll want to get thrown into the hellfire!
I'm falling!
What the hell?
You can't just kill other prisoners like that!
You want us to execute you right here?
No!
Your condition's been granted.
As for your end of the...
I'm aware of the deal.
I made a promise to you that I intend to live up to it.
Welcome back, sir!
It is very good to be back.
Show her to her quarters.
Yes, sir.
This way.
I'll bring your dinner immediately.
No need.
Reduce my servings from now on.
Are you certain about that?
How dare you question me!
Such insolence!
My apologies, madam.
Vice Admiral!
Yes, what now?
We just received a report that Red Hair had a run-in in the New World.
Shanks?
Are you sure about that one?
The timing doesn't make much sense.
Who did they say he was fighting?
Not one of us.
No.
Kaido of the Four Emperors.
Did you say Kaido?
That's correct, sir.
Apparently, Kaido was after Whitebeard.
I hear it was just a skirmish, but Shanks intercepted him.
I can't say to what end, though.
Bad tidings, but not unexpected.
These are turbulent waters indeed.
And a brush like this with the Four Emperors?
That's a deadly serious circumstance beyond our control.
With Whitebeard safe, he'll likely come after us.
I fear it may be all-out war.
You think his response will be that extreme, sir?
Whitebeard's men make up the strongest pirate crew in the world.
He'd be facing the entire navy, including three admirals, and the seven warlords of the sea.
No matter who comes out on top, this war will shape the very course of history.
Set sail for Marineford.
Yes, sir.
What the hell's going on?
The entire Upper Brass showed up here.
Magellan, Hannibal, and the Demon Guards?
I got a bad feeling something's about to go down.
This is murder.
Fashion your fireproof coat!
Straw Hat Luffy and the others should be coming out this door!
No update so far.
That's good.
Maybe they already got beaten by Minotaurus.
A true warden should face adversity instead of hiding.
Get your ugly mug out here!
Could you ward me first?
It's too bright!
When you inevitably pass this seat on to me, I'd appreciate it if you made it more open first.
Shut up! This seat was custom-made to my liking, and I like it closed, private, and dark.
It's a metaphor for how I feel about you.
It's coming!
Huh?
Ew.
Quiet! It's a toilet!
That is gross!
I can hear you!
Aw, if I'd have known we were just going to be standing around and waiting for them this long,
then I would have gone hunting.
Patience, Mistress Sadie, please.
Oh, it doesn't bother me.
But my boys here, they don't know what patience is.
Mmm.
The only thing they know is bloodlust.
The only thing I know is bloodlust.
Yeah, that is...
The only way I was produ compensate Pharmacists.
MacMு
I have an update!
Ah!
Straw Hat Luffy and the others are now located inside the well tower on level 3,
which means we're unfortunately unable to monitor them.
They've made it that far?
If they pull this off, all I have to do is lay blame on the warden.
Then I'll be...
It's not fair!
I really want to be warden.
Oh, I mean, I love you, Chair.
It'd make our lives a hell of a lot easier if they simply plummeted to their deaths from there.
The boiling pool of blood is right beneath them.
They all have devil fruit powers, after all.
They'd conveniently sink like stones.
If I die here, it's all your balls, Straw!
I don't want to go to level 4! It's hot enough already!
It's making it hot! We're headed for the pool of blood!
Man, this sucks!
Ah!
No!
Your voz!
Dark Horse-
Yeah I apologize.
Quiet Horse-
Taken staying.
Tirdy-
S 쪽 Cherry's
Steal rate!
S接下來 it's plainр Ar crazy!
Warr-
Tirdy-
Boa-
Dude, tirdy-
Tirdy-
I'm afraid that Straw Hat Luffy has already reached this level.
He didn't pass us. How is that possible?
He apparently fell down here through the well.
But the well leads directly to the pool of blood. How the hell are they alive?
From what I gathered, they used a massive piece of the falling floor to shield themselves and lead to safety.
The bastards have luck on their side.
One more thing!
What now?
It stinks, Warden.
I mean this situation, it stinks.
Well, sir, the demon guard Minotaurus also fell into the well, and apparently he's not moving.
Impossible! They defeated him?
It appears so.
The poor baby! I won't believe it!
Pull it together!
You will follow my orders carefully.
There are only two ways to get out of level four that don't include dying.
We have two staircases they can take that aren't currently protected by security guards.
From this point forward, we're splitting our forces into three.
Hanyabal, I want you in charge of this stairwell. Block all access to level three.
Mistress Sadie, I want you and the demon guards to defend the stairwell leading to level five.
No way! That sounds so boring. I want to punish those bad boys. Surely my outfit makes that clear enough to you.
Maybe I'll just let them slip past me and have the warden take the blame.
Any objections?
Oh, please, Warden. Don't do that.
But I didn't complain this time.
You don't need to. I can sense you plotting against me.
Oh, and once they're captured, you're free to do as you wish with them.
Oh, yes, sir. I can get behind that idea.
And as for the rest of the guards, I want you to pursue them at all costs.
You bring them to me dead or alive.
Sir!
Almost dead works, too.
This ends right now. They have toyed with me long enough.
We have a reputation to uphold.
The burning heat hell shall be their last stop.
But first...
Thornton's about to unleash his power!
You're dumping again?
Dammit!
The floor is insanely hot in here!
It's so hot my lungs feel like they're full of fire!
Now should we move them faster we get out of this place!
Now which way should we go?
You guys sound like babies.
Wily babies!
It's mind over matter. Just pretend the fire's your friend.
Honestly, I can't really blame you, though.
I do admit it's a little steamy in here, even compared to that desert.
Actually, maybe more than just a little...
My friend the fire might be turning on me.
Oh, crap!
Your blathering is worse than the damn heat!
I know which way!
Follow me!
Hey!
Where are you going?
So hot!
We're aware of that!
Huh.
Now where could our little straw boy be leading us?
Of course, to the kitchen!
Good, because I'm famished!
Wait for me, old chum!
I'm not gonna lie, food does sound good!
Kinda hoping for some food, too!
No! Wait a minute, buggy!
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
That food smells so good!
Hot, hot, hot, hot!
Oh, boy, I can't wait for Yanni food's eyes!
It's a straw hat movie!
Dang, there's a bunch of them!
Oh, this heat's beating me down!
But I'll get my energy back once I get some food in me!
Stop right there!
Kum-kum!
Firewall!
We have found straw hat Luffy, sir!
Team A's locked in battle with him now!
Team B has just arrived, too!
They've joined up with Team A, and they're closing in on him!
They don't seem to be holding up too well, though!
Both teams are requesting the same backup, sir!
What should we do?
Hmm?
Kum-kum!
Woo-hoo!
Wooah!
Oh!
AROUND AND AROUND AND AROUND I GO!
Around and around I go,
I'll come my way, Kim Poe,
Memoirs of a Summer's Day!
A and B teams have been wiped out.
C, D, and E have major losses.
Extra Becca from upstairs won't cut it.
They're too powerful for us.
We can't hold the position.
Oh, woe is me.
If only I were Warden, I could fix this.
Waaaaaahhh!
What are you freaking out about, partner?
Open your eyes and take a look.
Meh.
There's an ocean of guards down there.
And think, this level is devoted to the agony of the prisoners,
yet there's not a single guard manning the fire torture pit.
Waaaaaah!
Let's go!
Get a move on!
The first thing we should do is to check the staircases.
I've got a feeling they ambushed us.
With all these guards, they probably boxed us in on this level.
What if they've been waiting on level four this whole time?
That means they just want Straw Hat!
We weren't even trying to come down here!
Maybe not, but we are still trying to break out and they do know our names and faces.
Still, there's something even more troubling.
If they're sending this many guards after us, it's extremely likely they're also sending in the Impel Down All-Stars to put an end to this chaos.
And I'm not just talking about the other three demon guards, either.
Warden Magellan himself might make an appearance, and then we're dead, my friend.
Get out of my way!
Help!
Just give up!
Quit blocking the phone!
Whoa!
Rick me out!
I thought it was a spear or something heading at me.
What is that?
Gross!
Is it jelly or poop?
Huh?
Oh no, no!
.
It's time to put an end to your buffoonery once and for all, boy.
Who are you?
It's Magellan!
I've got you now, you criminal scum!
Magellan finally reveals himself and Luffy stands up to his fearsome Venom Venom power,
even knowing that a single touch of the Warden's deadly poison could lead to his death.
When Bon Clay cowers before the might of Magellan's Hydra,
is it a show of weakness or is the situation truly hopeless after all?
On the next, One Piece, Mighty Magellan, Bon Clay bugs out!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!